(Yowayowa Sensei)
Sensei actually moved in next door to me.
How am I going to handle that?
(Episode 3: Communicate through Rubbing)
No, calm down.
I should keep a distance from her.
Even if we're neighbors,
we probably won't interact much.
Um…
Good morning.
Sensei?
G-good morning.
I need to find a normal topic.
Akihito.
Why are you there?
W-wait, Ms. Akemi.
What a mess.
Hiyo was so flustered during the move
that she lost some important documents.
I was going
SISTER'S A NURSE AND CRAZY BUSY
to help her look for them,
but the hospital just called me in.
Could you help Hiyo find them?
I-it's fine.
I can find them by myself.
Don't worry.
We're neighbors.
We should help each other.
O-okay.
Even though Sensei just moved in,
I should not be alone with her
in her house.
HEART POUNDING
No…
I need to focus on finding the documents.
You're looking for
the handout notes for class, right?
Y-yes.
I stayed up all night making handouts
based on each student's weaknesses.
SOUND ASLEEP
But I accidentally fell asleep
and packed them up with everything else.
She tailored them individually?
And she pulled all-nighters for that?
I can't believe she went that far for us.
B-but
I only referred to students
by their seat numbers.
There's no personal information.
That's definitely important.
Let's keep looking then.
Okay.
RUSTLING
GRABBING
S-sorry.
S-sensei.
HEART FLUTTERING
Does she usually wear that kind of underwear?
It's not like that!
A clerk strongly recommended it
when I was at the store.
I just couldn't refuse.
They'd definitely be happy to see it.
Who?
Even against salespeople,
Yowayowa-sensei is weak.
S-so this isn't my daily underwear.
I'm not wearing it for anyone to see.
But it was expensive,
so not wearing it feels wasteful.
Functionally, it's perfectly fine.
So I still wear it on holidays.
She just confessed everything.
I'll go check out the other boxes then.
Okay, thank you.
PILED UP
These are my plushies.
So this is where they were.
I thought about leaving them at my parents' house,
but I felt too lonely without them.
So you like fish?
Yes, fish are my favorite.
Marine creatures
come in all shapes
and have unique ecosystems.
They're absolutely adorable.
And they're delicious too.
She thinks they're cute,
but still eats them?
This is called a tongue-eating louse.
It's a parasite that lives
on or inside sea bream.
Oh, sorry.
I got carried away when chatting.
I should hurry and find those handouts.
She looks so happy. It's cute.
Not here.
Did I leave them at my parents' house?
It's fine.
I'll just remake them tonight.
Is she pulling another all-nighter?
Let's keep looking.
I'll stay as long as it takes.
Is this it?
Y-yes!
Thank you.
I worked really hard on these.
I'll thank you properly next time…
STUMBLING
Careful!
S-sorry, I'm so clumsy.
I've troubled you again.
Since it's a holiday today,
she's wearing that underwear.
Abikura-kun,
someone as well-behaved as you
might be able to make that child open up.
Well-behaved?
That's how it is.
So Sensei and I went together
to the home of a student who hasn't attended school
since the new semester began.
In other words,
YUKISHITA
the home of a truant.
It seems Sensei comes daily
to deliver notes to his house.
SQUEEZING
What… what is he doing?
Who are you?
That's my line.
He… he's our class president.
Abikura-kun.
Class president?
I never allowed you to bring him here.
Idiot.
He called me an idiot?
Anyway…
Are you the truant student?
I thought he was
some elementary school kid.
I'm not called "you".
ASSERTIVELY
I am Yuuki Yukishita.
What's he being so cocky for?
TOUCHING
What?
Wait a… second.
SQUEEZING
Let go of her now!
A… Abikura-kun, don't get angry.
This child must just be lonely,
or just craving love.
But this guy…
Let me go, you creep.
Don't hold me like you're carrying a cat.
This must be
a unique way of communicating.
EXCITEDLY
Communicating by squeezing people.
There's no way that's true.
This won't do, Sensei is too kind.
Sensei,
can I speak with this student alone
for a minute?
S…sure, of course.
Come over here.
Do your best.
What for?
Don't just barge into others' houses.
That's trespassing.
This brat.
Who's the real criminal here?
How could you do that to a woman?
Sensei is just too kind to get angry.
But what you did is already a crime.
Shut up.
Truant students are usually sensitive.
If your words hurt my feelings
and make me hate school even more,
what then?
Would a sensitive person grope Sensei?
Idiot.
Thanks to Hiwamura,
I finally started to open up a little.
At first, I thought she was
some kind of monster and got scared.
But she came every day.
After talking to her,
I realized she's super weak
but very interesting.
Although what he says is true,
he has a really sharp tongue.
And her breasts are huge,
and that's really attractive.
You must have your eyes on those too.
Don't lump me in with you.
Anyway,
if a stranger kept touching you,
you'd feel uncomfortable too, right?
Do unto others as you would
have them do unto you.
Do you understand?
I can't help it.
I'm always alone.
I have no idea
how to interact with people.
Sorry.
Did you think I'd say that? Idiot.
Do unto others as you would
have them do unto you?
No one's ever done that to me,
so of course I don't understand.
Idiot, go die.
POUTING
This… darn brat.
Watch this.
This is exactly what I meant.
You find it annoying, don't you?
It feels kind of soft.
You're a girl?
Hiwamura!
That guy groped my chest.
Th…this is a misunderstanding, Sensei.
Yukishita has
RUBBING
established rubbing-based communication
with someone else?
RUBBING
That's also a misunderstanding.
Anyway, I apologize.
I'm really sorry.
I've been traumatized.
Such a rude person at school
makes me even more unwilling to go.
How… how could this be?
DISPIRITED
I'm really sorry, it's all my fault.
Don't say that.
I should've told you she's a girl.
I didn't mean to force her
to go to school.
I just thought
visiting her place every day
might expand her world a little.
But I hope that one day
she'll come to school on her own.
CHOKING UP
I didn't expect it to turn out like this.
(Yowayowa Sensei)
THE NEXT DAY
Hiwamura!
FLAT
This… this isn't what I wanted.
What's this? Why are you here again?
I have nothing to say to a pervert
who randomly gropes people.
STARING
Go back!
This sounds so harsh.
No, I need to calm down.
I'm here to apologize for yesterday.
I offended you yesterday. I'm sorry.
But there's something I must say.
You seemed so thrilled
just by touching the chest.
Isn't that a bit shallow?
What?
You can only chat with Sensei
after school, right?
If you come to school,
whether in homeroom meeting or class,
you'll see something more attractive…
Boring.
Everyone is like this.
Saying that school is fun.
Maybe you'll see
a more attractive side of Sensei.
You… you mean…
You did things more bold
with Hiwamura at school?
Ye… yes.
Re… really?
She's taken the bait.
Li… like what?
I can't say it, it's too risque.
EXCITED
Too risque to be mentioned? Amazing.
During the time I didn't attend school,
has school turned into a risque haven?
Envious, aren't you?
This is the reward for attending school.
School's actually not so bad.
Hiwamura, I'm going to school.
She changed her mind so easily.
If that's the case, I'll go to school.
A… Abikura-kun,
what on earth did you do?
I'm sorry, Sensei.
But I have one condition.
Let me squeeze your chest one last time.
This brat…
No way this is her last time.
I…
Okay.
Sensei?
TIGHTFITTING
Somehow it feels…
I guessed you would say that.
So… I took off my bra.
It's my fault
for your bad impression of each other.
So I must take responsibility.
For Yukishita's forgiveness,
I have no choice but to do this.
She has… a strong resolve.
What… what's this?
Are you a nympho?
Maybe.
SQUEEZE
Wait, Yukishita.
But it's great
that there's one more student
who understands Sensei.
Despite her faults,
she can see that Sensei isn't scary.
She shouldn't be a bad person.
FLUSTERED
No bra is amazing.
So the touch before was fake?
She shouldn't be a bad person…
GOING UNDER
Wait!
PINCH
That's just too much.
What?
Hey, Abikura.
She actually came.
It's quite something
that you came to school.
If there's anything in class
you don't understand…
Class? What are you talking about?
I only come to school to see
BRAZEN
the risque Hiwamura.
You took that seriously?
And look at her.
June starts today,
Hiwamura has changed into summer clothes.
SQUEEZING
Scored big already.
Awesome.
I can actually understand that.
Yu…Yukishita?
I'm really happy you came to school.
If you have any problems,
feel free to tell me anytime.
Mhm.
Don't do anything weird to Sensei, okay?
Don't do anything weird?
Then I'm definitely gonna do it!
I'm gonna
fully enjoy the lucky pervert events
WATCH THIS
I'm gonna fully enjoy the lucky pervert events
that only happen at school.
WATCH THIS
I'll have an amazing pervy school life.
She's so cute.
First up is the classic.
Bumping into Hiwamura at a corner
and burying my face
BURYING
in her chest.
Thank you.
Go!
The wrong person!
Ouch.
SQUEEZING
STARTLED
So…sorry, sensei!
I…it's fine.
HEART POUNDING
Why does his touch feel more perverted than mine?
Then onto the next classic.
Accidentally barging
into the changing room
AH
and making Hiwamura scream.
Whoops, my hand slipped.
First, get Hiwamura's clothes dirty.
You can't attend class like this.
Go put on this outfit that I lend you.
Wait, Yukishita.
And the outfit I just gave her
is actually a bunny girl costume.
Changing into
a bunny girl costume at school…
Found her.
The gal squad.
Oh no… they're gonna yell at me.
You're adorable!
TIGHT HUG
Nice to meet you, I'm Mizuki Mukubayashi.
Play with me, okay?
Wait, Mizuki.
You'll crush her to death!
I almost died back there.
But that feeling wasn't bad.
SORRY
Hiwamura's gone.
Is she mad at me?
Yukishita.
Next class isn't that way.
Shut up, leave me alone.
Usually it's just Hiwamura
and me chatting at home.
Today I've just been
sneaking around after her,
with no chance to be together with her.
I haven't talked to her at all.
And I even made her angry.
This isn't how it should be.
I shouldn't have come to school.
Yu…Yukishita?
I finally found you. Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I…
Hi…Hiwamura, that outfit…
After I changed, you disappeared.
While searching for you,
Abikura-kun told me
you seemed down
and asked me to check on you.
Abikura said that?
I'm sorry, Yukishita.
It's your first day in school.
It must be tough.
I should've paid attention
to how you were feeling.
Hiwamura.
No, it's all my fault.
I bumped into you and stained your shirt.
That's nothing.
It's a teacher's duty
to work hard for students.
If there's anything else you want to do,
just tell me.
Hiwamura.
Then I want to see you in another outfit.
Are those two okay?
Um…
This outfit is just…
BLUSHING
A…Abikura-kun!
Yowayowa bunny girl spotted on campus.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Go…Good morning.
STARTLED
Sorry.
Our homeroom teacher
works really hard.
DEJECTED
But everyone thinks she's scary.
CLASS 2-2
That's how it is.
FOREST SCHOOL
To clear up misunderstandings about Hiwamura-sensei,
the Yowayowa Team is
officially established.
MEMBER NO. 2
That's right.
TOUGH GIRL, MIZUKI MUKUBAYASHI
I'm gonna put some real thought into this.
COSPLAY CATALOG
The desk broke!
MEMBER NO. 3
What should I make her wear next?
CHEST-RUBBING SHORT GIRL, YUUKI YUKISHITA
MEMBER NO. 1
These members are a headache.
MR. MEDIOCRACY, ABIKURA
Hey, Abikura.
I need to talk to you.
HUGGING
You hugged the wrong person again.
No, I didn't.
U-um…
You told Hiwamura that I seemed down…
Th-thanks.
She's being so honest today.
POUNCING
Yuki, hug me too!
Didn't I tell you that hurts?
Mukubayashi is an idiot.
SQUEEZING
Th-they're already getting along.
As expected of a super-social gal.
So her sudden honesty
was Mukubayashi's doing too?
I'll get you back…
Her rubbing-based communication
strategy actually worked.
By the way,
Abikura, why are you so close with Yuki?
First the teacher, and now a kid?
Hey, Yukishita is of our age.
And stop saying things
that could be misinterpreted.
You're always like this.
Making friends behind my back
without telling me.
I am your childhood friend,
idiot Abikura!
VIBRATING
What the heck is she doing?
Let's get back on track…
Today I wanted to discuss how to clear up
the misunderstandings about Hiwamura-sensei.
Nobody believes what I say either.
Mizuki, you've been fooled.
There's no way Kowakowa-sensei
could be that approachable.
The rumors are so bad
even the Tough Girl can't fix them.
So,
our second-year Forest School trip
is coming up soon.
It's three days and two nights.
We'll have more time together than usual.
To make everyone realize how kind she is,
this is our only chance.
I see.
So what's the plan?
That's what we need to
brainstorm together now.
Huh? You're all here?
Sensei?
Hiwamura.
Hiyori, what are you wearing?
Cosplay? That's cute!
Can I squeeze…?
On the second day of Forest School,
I was assigned as a scarer
for the test of courage.
Why'd she have to play that role?
That's way too perfect casting.
If we let sensei scare people,
everyone will just fear her more.
By the way, what are you all doing here?
CLEARING UP MISUNDERSTANDINGS
ABOUT HIWAMURA-SENSEI
FOREST SCHOOL
The plan is exposed.
The Yowayowa Ghost was so shocking
I forgot to cover it.
You…
You'd do this for me?
S-sorry for making you worry about me.
N-no, don't say that.
But I'll be fine.
I'll handle my own problems.
Just enjoy yourselves
during Forest School.
MOVED
Hiyori…
Then let's try other cosplays.
That'll make us happier.
O-oh, okay.
What's this? Now I'm getting excited.
Hey, what're you doing?
Aren't we discussing?
You really don't get it, do you?
If she dresses as a cute monster,
ASSERTIVELY
they will understand her charm.
Th-that makes sense.
HOSPITAL
Like a blood-soaked nurse.
Injection.
Or maybe a zombie.
Awesome! Hiyori's super photogenic.
I can't hold back.
Who'd care about the test of courage
seeing Hiwamura like that?
These two are just using her as a toy.
Next up is Mummy Girl.
U-um, this is way too revealing.
And it's hard to move around.
Careful!
MAID OUTFIT
Sensei says she'll be fine,
but I still hope to use this school camp
to clear the misunderstanding
between her and the students.